musikupdate.com 2017-10-24

# Privacy Policy - MusikUpdate

**Privacy Policy:** Last updated on October 21, 2015 **  
**

**What information does ,Musikupdate collect?**

**Musikupdate**  collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What does musikudpate use your information for?**

Any of the information **Musikupdate** collects from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To personalize your experience  
(your information helps **Musikupdate** to better respond to your individual needs)

– To improve **Musikupdate**  
( **Musikupdate** continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback **Musikupdate** receive from you)

– To improve customer service  
(your information helps **Musikupdate** to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

– To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

– To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How does **Musikupdate** protect your information?**

**Musikupdate** implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Musikupdate** offers the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Does Musikupdateuse cookies?**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Does Musikupdate disclose any information to outside parties?**

**Musikupdate** does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist **Musikupdate** in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. **Musikupdate** may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, **Musikupdate** may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because **Musikupdate** value your privacy, **Musikupdate** has taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. **Musikupdate** therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.musikupdate.com](http://www.musikupdate.com/)

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Advertising**

Any advertisements served on Musikupdate may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow advertisers to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use advertising services. Learn how to opt out of these advertising cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by them through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If Musikupdate decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact **Musikupdate** using the information below.

www.musikupdate.com  
Lagos, Lagos State, Nigeria.

Did you find apk for android? You can find new [Free Android Games](https://dlandroid24.com/) and apps.
